## **Daniel Ardekani**

Chester Springs, PA | 610-800-1303 | ardekanicapital@gmail.com | github.com/danardekani | danardekani.github.jo

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Since my transition into technology, I have had the opportunity to work on a wide range of technical projects with both government agencies and private companies. Being involved in so many projects. I have had the opportunity to see how the public and private sectors operate. I have had the privilege to be a part of projects as a developer, business analyst, and IT consultant. I have been very fortunate to gain these experiences throughout my career and believe I could be great asset for your any team.

#### SKILLS

Technical: Microsoft Office 365, Teams, Power Apps, Power Automate, SharePoint Online, OneDrive, Dynamics 365, PowerBi, Azure Cloud, Azure Automation, Function Apps, Storage Accounts, Resource Groups, Active Directory, Logic Apps, Key Vault, and App registrations, PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL Server, Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, Vue.is, HTML5, CSS, Git, RESTful APIs

Additional: Agile Development, Project Management, IT Consulting, Business Analysis, Stakeholder Management, Requirements Documentation, Business Process Workflows, Data Gateways, Kali Linux, Python, PowerShell

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **PSA Financial-SharePoint Migration**

December 19'

**Business Application Consultant** 

- PSA Financial needed a solution to migrate its legacy file system into SharePoint.
- PSA required that each of their 25,000 files has its own site and standard template.
- Modified SharePoint collection template and applied it files using Azure Storage, runbooks, Logic Apps, and stored all of the site collections under a SharePoint hub. Skills: SharePoint Online, Azure Automation, Azure Storage, Logic Apps, Microsoft Teams,

# PowerShell scripting

**Hamilton Associates- Power Apps & SQL Integration** 

November 19'

**Business Application Consultant** 

- Hamilton was looking to move away from its legacy file maker to a more modern, user-friendly, and robust solution.
- To meet their requirements, I built a Power App with a modern design that enabled users to create, edit, and delete files.
- To pull documents into the application, I set up a data gateway to their on-premise SQL server. Skills: Power Apps, Data Gateway, Microsoft SQL Server, Microsoft Teams, Microsoft Dynamics 365, Data Visualization

## Office of the Assistant Secretary for Health (OASH)- ERM Project

March 19'

- **Business Analyst** 
  - OASH required an ERM system with the capabilities of storing, routing, and tracing various document formats.
  - OASH needed the ability to route documents internally and externally when working with outside agencies.
  - I led requirements gathering meetings, developed workflows using BPMN, created and maintained documentation, and created user stories.

**Skills**: requirements, user stories, design, business analysis, process re-engineering, Microsoft Teams, Microsoft Dynamics 365

### **Actualize Coding Bootcamp- WodUp**

August 19'

Developer

- Created web application for CrossFit athletes to track WODs (workout of the day), personal stats, connect with others, and submit scores and times against a global leader board that can be filtered by workout type, gender, age, country, and gym affiliate.
- The app was created using Ruby, Rails, Vue.js, and Postgres.
  Skills: Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Vue.js, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### INCITE AUTOMATION, BALTIMORE, MD

**Business Application Consultant** 

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019

- Developed enterprise applications using Power Automate, PowerApps, and the Azure cloud platform.
- Created Flows and Logic Apps to streamline historically slow and tedious business processes.
- Developed SharePoint sites to customer specification and managed site and user permissions.
- Created PowerApps to enhance user experiences manipulating data such as a SQL table or SharePoint list.
- Customized and configured Dynamics 365 to create business processes, forms, and relationships.

#### DATA FEDERAL, Columbia, MD

**Business Analyst** 

Dec 2018 - Nov 2019

- Build essential relationships with customers and stakeholders.
- Elicit project requirements and design workflows using business processes model notation (bpmn).
- Provide and document system analysis for customers with viable replacement options.
- Create and maintain Azure backlog.
- Create and maintain living requirements documents.
- Develop, document and revise system design procedures, test procedures, and quality standards.

#### GOOD LIFE COMPANIES, Reading, PA

Director of Revenue Generation

Sep 2018 - Jan 2018

- Created digital marketing lead generation program for Good Life independent financial advisers to expand advisory practice using SEO and SEM.
- Created digital marketing department for advisors to leverage their personal brand.
- Project manager and product owner of investment mobile app that would help advisor clients easily access financial data and create auto deposits into their investment accounts.

Digital Marketing Strategist

Aug 2018 – Sep 2018

• Strategic digital marketing for the purposes of expanding Good Life Companies online presence and generating new lead sources.

Wealth Manager

*May 2016 – Sep 2018* 

• Helped clients with retirement, education, and insurance planning.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### ALVERNIA UNIVERSITY, Reading, PA

Bachelor of Science in Business Management & Minor in Economics, May 2016

- Men's Varsitu Soccer
- 3.34 GPA

#### Actualize Coding Bootcamp, Chicago, IL

#### Certificate in Full Stack Software Development, August 2019

• **Bootcamp:** Completed the intensive, 4-month Actualize bootcamp and learned Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, Postgres, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git, and Vue.js. Learned how to think like a software engineer and gained the ability to tackle any new technology.

NYU- Tandon School of Engineering, Manhattan, NY (Online Master of Science in Cybersecurity, May 2020- December 2022